<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pico</title><link>https://okniro.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Pico</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://okniro.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My New Website is Live!</title><link>https://okniro.github.io/blog/new_website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://okniro.github.io/blog/new_website/</guid><description>Hey there, amazing folks!
You probably noticed by now, but if you didn&amp;rsquo;t: I now have a website!
I&amp;rsquo;m Niro and I had the privilege of making a difference in people&amp;rsquo;s lives (and their families lives!) through caregiving.
What&amp;rsquo;s planned for the website, you ask? Interesting reads: I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing articles about caregiving. Heartfelt stories: Get ready for some personal stories from my time as a PSW. Useful tools and websites about caregiving.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://okniro.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://okniro.github.io/about/</guid><description>I truly believe that compassionate care is at the heart of caregiving. I genuinely care and treat every client with the respect, dignity, and kindness they deserve.
Life can be unpredictable, and I understand that. I have a flexible schedule to accommodate client&amp;rsquo;s lifestyle and evolving needs.</description></item><item><title>My skills</title><link>https://okniro.github.io/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://okniro.github.io/skills/</guid><description>Personal care Bathing, dressing, grooming, and mobility Medication management and administration Meal preparation Specialized care Tailored services for clients with specific medical conditions. Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s care Hospice care Dementia care EMR systems Mobility Assisting with errands, medical appointments, and grocery shopping. Housekeeping Light housekeeping and maintaining a clean and safe living environment Laundry</description></item></channel></rss>